[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ somber, melancholy music playing]
THE LATE JEONG MINJAE
[sighs softly]
[woman sobbing]
Why did you do that?
Minjae isn't even a detective anymore.
Why?
He's not a cop!
My poor Minjae. What am I going to do?
[sobbing] Minjae.
[wails] Minjae!
Minjae!
[wailing bitterly]
- [voice shaking] I'm sorry.
- Minjae!
I'm so sorry.
[woman continues wailing]
[♪ music fades]
GANGHA JUNGANG HOSPITAL FUNERAL HALL
Ah. I'll catch up with you later.
Okay.
EPISODE 13
[engine starts]
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
THE LITTLE PRINCE
[bang]
[Seongwon] Don't run away from this.
Once you accept it,
you'll finally be free.
After all, you're my Little Prince.
THE LITTLE PRINCE
I HAD TO DRAW THE INSIDE
OF THE BOA CONSTRICTOR
YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO EXPLAIN EVERYTHING TO GROWN-UPS
[Seongwon] The moment I first met you
is one of them.
Me?
At the gathering?
You don't remember, do you?
We met way before that.
When I was just a kid.
I've liked you ever since then.
Back then,
you were a lot quieter than you are now.
You were shorter and thinner.
The hallway was bright,
and a breeze was
coming in through the window.
SEO YUKYUNG PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
[Seongwon] How's my drawing?
It's really good.
Do you know what this is?
It's a puppy.
[Seongwon] My picture.
Everyone said it was weird.
You were the only person
who complimented me.
[Dr. Seo] Jin Isoo.
Come inside.
[♪ somber, suspenseful music continues]
KEEP QUIET
[door closes]
[♪ music fades]
Yu Seongwon.
Do you remember him?
Yu Seongwon?
Did he kill someone?
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
What makes you think that?
Because he was
captivated by death as a child.
He first came to my clinic
when he was nine years old.
[♪ music turns ominous]
SEO YUKYUNG PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
Him.
Can you make him normal?
[scoffs softly]
[exhales shakily]
I think he's insane.
Move.
Out of my way!
- [screams]
- Mom, what do you think you're doing?
[♪ music fades]
Jackie is dead.
JACKIE
You know, don't you?
Did Jackie bite you?
He always does.
Apparently, he thinks he's above me.
I see.
You must've resented Jackie.
[scoffs softly]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
After Jackie died,
how did you feel?
It was nice.
He doesn't bark or bite me anymore.
He listens to me now.
Can you draw Jackie for me?
[♪ tinkling, ominous music playing]
[steady pencil scratching]
He never once drew a dog that was alive.
[♪ music fades]
Still, he got better
with art therapy and counseling,
and nothing happened for a while,
but it flared up again
after the chairman passed away.
He saw the dead body
and was inspired.
[monitor flatlining]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[inhales sharply]
What's going on?
Your son has locked the door.
[sighs in exasperation]
Yu Seongwon!
[yelling] Yu Seongwon!
[♪ music increases in tempo]
- [knocking on door]
- Open the door.
[yelling] Yu Seongwon, open the door!
[breathing heavily]
[♪ music swells]
[loud bang]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[♪ ominous sting plays]
What do you think?
The title is "Marionette."
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[exhales shakily]
[softly] Crazy bastard.
Do you like it?
Get this crazy bastard out of here.
[exclaiming]
Stop it! Let go!
No, seriously!
Stop it!
Let go of me!
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
Nothing...
happened here.
If this gets out,
this hospital is finished.
We'll be careful, ma'am.
Take this off! [exclaims, screams]
Take it off!
[screaming]
[Dr. Seo] In the end, he was
hospitalized for a very long time.
[distorted screaming]
[Dr. Seo] I helped Seongwon
channel his fantasies about death
into works of art.
[♪ music swells, fades]
I heard he became a famous artist.
What exactly did he do?
He's been involved in six cases so far.
Two were his models.
He's killing people to create his pieces.
It looks like
my treatment failed after all.
You know Seongwon likes you, don't you?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
He said you alone understood him.
What is his weakness?
Please help me.
His weakness?
[♪ music turns ominous]
[inhales sharply]
There was one final piece he made
while he was hospitalized.
It was also of a dog.
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
Jackie's collar was wrapped around it.
Then, even now,
he must have the victims' belongings.
To relive the thrill of his killings,
I'm sure that somewhere,
he would have displayed
his victims' belongings.
Like works of art.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
JO NAYEONG, CHOI YEONGMIN,
KIM HEEJUN, JEONG MINJAE
YU SEONGWON
UBS CHAIRWOMAN'S SON, FAMOUS SCULPTOR
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[sighs heavily]
The day before she went missing,
Jo Nayeong went
to Yu Seongwon's studio in his car.
On the 12th, he dropped her off at CONEX.
She was last seen
on camera in the corridor.
But there's no footage
of her leaving CONEX.
[Junyoung] Choi Yeongmin said
he had his modeling job on the eighth.
The next morning, on the ninth,
he drove his car from the studio,
parked it, then disappeared.
And Kim Heejun said he was
going to meet Yu Seongwon.
[Kyungjin] But he left his car
at Deoksan-ri and disappeared.
Lastly, Jeong Minjae,
who was following Yu Seongwon...
[Kyungjin] His car was found
near the Hangang River.
They all follow a similar pattern.
The victims were all with Yu Seongwon,
then the next day, in a crowded place,
or somewhere too far out
for the camera to make out their face,
they left their car and vanished.
Then when and how did he kill them?
Did Yu Seongwon lure them
into meeting him again somewhere else?
But for the days the victims went missing,
Yu Seongwon has a solid alibi.
[sighs heavily]
[♪ music fades]
JEONG MINJAE DETECTIVE AGENCY
CEO JEONG MINJAE
SHADOW WITHOUT A TRACE
TRACK TO THE END
[♪ somber, suspenseful music playing]
- [mouse clicks]
- [sighs heavily]
[mouse clicks]
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
YU SEONGWON
JEONG MINJAE
VEHICLE STOP LOCATION
65, EUNDAM-RO 13BEON-GIL, GANGHA-GU
ALL NOTES
SONG AREUM
65, EUNDAM-RO 13BEON-GIL, GANGHA-GU
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
- Hey, you're here.
- Did you see all the files?
Yeah.
But all the victims were still alive
the day after they met Yu Seongwon.
We can't figure out
when and how he killed them.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Our theory is...
that this person is Yu Seongwon.
The victims were probably killed
on the day they met Yu Seongwon.
He wanted to leave proof
they were alive the next day,
so Yu Seongwon went out himself.
He put on their clothes to look like them,
went to a crowded place,
and then disappeared.
That's why these were classified
as missing-person cases.
Yeah, that makes more sense.
[softly] Wow!
He's one scary guy, that Yu Seongwon.
[exhales deeply]
- [Areum] Yu Seongwon?
- [♪ music fades]
No, he didn't come here.
Ah, I see.
Are there security cameras
in this building?
There's one on the first floor,
but it's broken.
I kept asking them to fix it,
but they never did.
[♪ pensive music playing]
Why do you ask?
My colleague,
who was following Yu Seongwon,
died.
I think he was kidnapped around here.
[Areum] Oh, my God.
Was Yu Seongwon behind it?
That's very likely.
Come to think of it, that day,
just after I'd arrived home,
I heard something strange.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[muffled clattering]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[line connects, ringing]
[♪ music fades]
If this is Yu Seongwon,
who drove this car?
I don't know who it is,
but it means he has an accomplice.
I know who the accomplice is.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
This is...
[Hyera] Yes.
The man who's always
by Yu Seongwon's side, right?
That man lives with him in the studio,
so I figured he would know something.
But he was an accomplice.
Do you know who he is?
Not really. He's just called "Mr. Hwang."
He's looked after the Yu family's villa
since Seongwon was a child.
His studio used to be their villa.
Whatever Yu Seongwon says,
that man obeys.
Hey, Hwang. Bring me some more chocolate.
Hey, aren't you being a bit too rude?
Don't call him "Hwang."
But I don't know his name.
It's fine. He's my servant.
His father was also
a servant to my family.
But he messed up big time and almost died,
then my dad saved him.
[chuckles]
That's why he's my servant.
Right, Hwang?
Yes, Young Master.
[chuckling]
[♪ music fades]
First, let's check UBS's employee list.
Okay.
- Check who's registered at the studio.
- Got it.
[sighs heavily]
Are you okay?
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
[inhales shakily]
I'm just going to focus
on catching Yu Seongwon for now.
Right, let's do that.
[Isoo sighs softly]
UBS EMPLOYEE LIST
REGISTERED RESIDENTS RECORD
- Did you find him?
- [♪ music fades]
He's not here. Not in the employee list,
or at the address.
Let's just bring him in for questioning.
If he gets out after that, he might run.
Should I go talk to him?
[Hyera exhales sharply]
I don't know if that's the right approach.
If he's completely on Yu Seongwon's side,
it might backfire on us.
[sighs in exasperation]
We need a reason to make a move.
[sighs heavily]
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
[Junyoung sighs softly]
[camera shutters clicking]
The inside of the car
has been wiped clean.
[sighs defeatedly]
[♪ music swells, fades]
- Sir.
- What is it?
[♪ music turns ominous]
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
[cell phone vibrating]
Yes, sir.
Right. Please send it over right away.
We found a fingerprint
on Jeong Minjae's car.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[digital beeping]
NAME, HWANG JONGSU
CRIMINAL RECORD, 4 PRIORS
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Hwang Jongsu, age 59.
[Isoo] He's a former gang member
with priors for drugs and fatal assault.
Let's go bring him in.
- [Junyoung] Okay.
- [Kyungjin] Okay.
DETECTIVE DIVISION
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music fades]
1 DAY EARLIER
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[Seongwon sighs softly]
Do you know where Police Chief Hwang is?
Yes, he's in prison.
That's not someone else's problem.
It could happen to you, too.
Even if you lived
an honest life in public service,
I can make that happen to you.
But I doubt you were that honest.
[chuckles smugly]
Leave my son alone.
Keep me updated on the investigation.
[exhales shakily]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[siren blaring]
DETECTIVE DIVISION
VIOLENT CRIME INVESTIGATION
TEAM 1, TEAM 2
[exhales heavily]
[exhales softly]
[call phone vibrating]
Yes, sir.
[Taegyun] So, how did it go?
Fingerprint? You found a fingerprint?
Yes, sir. Team 1 has identified him.
His name is Hwang Jongsu.
Right, okay.
FINGERPRINT SEARCH RESULTS
NAME, HWANG JONGSU
[cell phone vibrating]
- Hello?
- [Taegyun] Hello, ma'am?
I don't think you need to worry anymore.
We have a suspect now.
His name is Hwang Jongsu.
He has a criminal record.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music continues]
[line disconnects]
[cell phone vibrates]
JEONG TAESEON
MR. HWANG HAS BEEN FLAGGED
[♪ music swells]
[exhales deeply]
[♪ music fades]
[slurps]
[Seongwon] Have you finished eating?
Yes, I've finished. [clearing throat]
[Mr. Hwang clears throat]
[gulps] Yes.
I heard you owe my dad big time.
Yes.
He saved my life.
[Seongwon] Mmm.
I heard that before he died,
he told you to protect me no matter what.
Yes, that's right.
Now's that time.
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[chuckling smugly]
Time to repay what you owe.
[Mr. Hwang sighs softly]
[Seongwon exhales deeply]
Run for your life.
Make sure...
you don't get caught.
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[siren blaring]
[♪ dramatic, ominous sting plays]
- [engine revs]
- [tires screech]
Hey, turn the car around.
Hwang Jongsu.
[tires screeching]
[♪ gripping instrumental music playing]
[siren continues blaring]
[tires screech]
[engine revving]
- [engine revving]
- [tires screech]
Hwang Jongsu, stop the car!
Mr. Hwang! Stop the car!
- [tires screech]
- [metallic crunch]
- [Isoo grunts]
- [tires screeching]
- [all grunt]
- [Isoo panting]
- [engine revving]
- [tires screeching]
[Hyera breathing heavily]
- Follow him.
- [Kyungjin] Yes, ma'am.
[siren continues blaring]
[tires screeching]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[panting frantically]
[siren wailing distantly]
[siren approaches]
[siren blaring]
[siren stops]
[♪ music fades]
He's not here.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
- That way.
- Right.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[panting]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[wheezing, panting]
[cell phone vibrating]
[Mr. Hwang, panting] Ma'am, it's me.
Where are you?
The Myeongun-dong construction site.
[Taeseon] That's not far.
- Wait there.
- Yes, ma'am.
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[beeps]
[line ringing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[Mr. Hwang grunts softly]
[breath trembling, breathing heavily]
Mr. Hwang!
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[chuckles]
Young Master.
[exhales softly]
Can we
please talk?
Please go ahead.
[Mr. Hwang exhales softly]
We got a suicidal person.
Myeongun-dong construction site. Hurry.
[line disconnects]
We're not here
to arrest you.
I've done a lot of bad things in my life.
I deserve to die.
Mr. Hwang Jongsu.
You care about Yu Seongwon, right?
I do.
As much as my own life.
Before the chairman passed away,
he made me promise.
Then we need to stop him
from killing more people.
That's...
not something we can stop.
[Isoo exhales sharply]
First,
just come this way.
Come talk with me.
[Mr. Hwang] Young Master.
The chairman said to me
that I should let Seongwon
do whatever he wants.
If I can't, I should die.
Please come tell me...
what you mean by that.
Huh?
Even if I told you,
you wouldn't understand.
Mr. Hwang.
- [indistinct murmuring]
- [camera shutters clicking]
- [Junyoung] Stop filming!
- [Kyungjin] Stop filming!
- [Junyoung] I said, stop filming!
- [Kyungjin] Stop!
No filming. Cameras down.
- Police! No filming!
- [Junyoung] Cameras down!
[Kyungjin] Get down from there!
No filming!
Lower your cameras.
- [Junyoung] Cameras down!
- [Kyungjin] Lower your cameras!
- Stop filming.
- [Junyoung] No filming.
- Cameras down!
- [Kyungjin] Lower your cameras!
[distant clamoring continues]
They're here.
[Junyoung] Lower your cameras!
[distorted footsteps]
[dull thud]
- Stop filming.
- [heavy thud, squelch]
- [reporters gasps]
- [reporter 1] What's that?
[♪ somber music playing]
- [swears softly]
- [camera shutters clicking]
[frantic clamoring]
[Kyungjin] Stop filming!
No filming! Your cameras!
Turn off your cameras!
You can't film this!
- [reporter 2] Why?
- Stop filming!
- Hello? I'm at...
The suicidal person just...
Yes, Myeongun-dong.
Please could you hurry?
[Kyungjin] Lower your cameras!
You can't film this.
Turn off your cameras!
- Turn off your cameras!
- [breath trembling]
[Kyungjin] Lower your cameras!
Stop filming!
Stop filming! You can't film this!
[news channel audio fades]
Mmm.
[♪ music fades]
CHASING THE TRUTH OF THAT DAY
SPECIAL REPORT
ON JIN ISOO'S MURDER ALLEGATIONS
[♪ tense, dramatic music playing]
I stand before you again
after a long absence.
Given the gravity of the case,
I will personally lead
today's special broadcast.
Last night, a man fell from a building
at a deserted construction site.
To understand the full scope of this case,
we must begin
with the murder of Kim Younghwan.
Ten days ago, Mr. Kim Younghwan,
the CEO of a film production company,
was brutally murdered.
The prime suspect was
the victim's close friend
and the only person present at the scene,
Detective Jin Isoo.
There was compelling evidence,
but Detective Jin was released
without charge a few days later.
[Mujin] I thought it was unjust.
All the evidence pointed to him,
but he was released without charge.
I still think Jin Isoo is the killer.
Gangha Violent Crime next arrested
a new suspect, Mr. Cho.
However, in just a day,
he was poisoned to death while in custody.
Finally, last night,
a new suspect, Mr. Hwang,
fell to his death
while fleeing from police.
Can we really call this a coincidence?
Some speculate that in an attempt
to divert suspicion from himself,
Detective Jin tried to frame Mr. Hwang,
who has no connection to this case,
as a new suspect.
Was his hand
reaching out to save him?
Or was it to push him?
[♪ music fades]
- [TV beeps]
- [remote clatters]
She's spouting
whatever nonsense she wants.
She stepped in herself
as a former news anchor.
[sighs in exasperation]
By the way,
how did Hwang Jongsu know?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
It looked like he was running away.
How did he know that we suspected him?
[♪ music fades]
Team 1.
Effective immediately,
you are all suspended.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Joo Hyera, do you have something to say?
The suspect in Kim Younghwan's murder case
died while in custody,
a victim's dead body was delivered here,
and the suspect in that murder
committed suicide.
[Taegyun sighs wearily]
You deserve to be suspended, don't you?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Get lost, all of you!
Stay out of my sight!
[swears softly]
[mutters]
[door opens]
Chief.
[sighs softly]
Just stand down for now.
- But--
- Hyera.
If you keep this up,
you could lose your job.
How will you catch
Yu Seongwon as a civilian?
[sighs softly]
[♪ music swells, fades]
[knocking at door]
Come in.
- [door closes]
- I don't think it's even been 10 minutes
since I told you to stay out of my sight.
I'm here to make your wish come true, sir.
[grunts softly]
[clacks]
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
- [hand thuds on table]
- [exhales softly]
I'll leave.
That's your wish, isn't it?
So leave Detective Joo,
Detective Park, and Detective Choi alone.
[scoffs]
They're already done for.
There's going to be
a disciplinary hearing.
You can all leave hand in hand.
What exactly did we do wrong?
If anyone did anything wrong here,
it wasn't us.
It was you, sir.
[♪ gripping, dramatic music playing]
When we went,
Hwang Jongsu was already on the run.
As if he had already been warned.
I checked at the security office.
GANGHA POLICE STATION SECURITY OFFICE
Who did you call?
It was just a work call.
[Isoo] Sir.
Do you know who Hwang Jongsu is?
He's Yu Seongwon's closest associate.
He's protected Yu Seongwon
since Seongwon was a child.
If we're right and Yu Seongwon
committed murder in his studio,
Hwang Jongsu is both a witness
to everything and an accomplice.
Now do you understand what you did?
You leaked confidential information.
If you touch my team,
I'm going to expose it.
[♪ music swells]
- [♪ music fades]
- [sighs]
[Kyungjin sighs heavily]
[sighs defeatedly]
[♪ somber music playing]
[sighs heavily]
Detective Joo.
What do we do now?
[inhales deeply]
You'll be fine.
I'll find a way to stop it.
Hey, you're a detective.
This can happen while working a case.
No, that's not what I meant.
How do we catch Yu Seongwon?
The suspect's dead, and we're suspended.
Yu Seongwon won't stop.
What if he kills someone again?
- [sighs wearily]
- [door opens]
Why is everyone so down, huh?
What's this? You're clocking out already?
Unpack and get back to work.
I'm the only one leaving.
- What?
What are you talking about?
I made a deal with the police chief.
I'm the one he hates most.
I'll leave,
and you three won't be suspended.
[♪ gentle, somber music playing]
[sighs] Jin Isoo.
You guys don't have anywhere to go.
I've got plenty of other options.
Bro.
- Are you really going to quit?
- Yes.
I just went ahead
and handed the chief my resignation.
[Junyoung] Hey.
What do you think you're doing?
This case started because of me.
The press will come after me, too.
Staying will only make it harder.
I'll clear this up later.
Take care. I'm a free man now.
[door opens]
- [door closes]
- [sighs softly]
[Hyera panting]
Jin Isoo.
[continues panting]
I'm sorry.
Why do you look so defeated?
I'll go out and do what I can
on the outside.
You should
hold things down here.
I'm not giving up on Yu Seongwon.
I'll catch him no matter what.
[♪ music fades]
Mr. Jin Isoo is here.
Hello!
Are you here to complain?
No, I came to thank you.
I'm a civilian now, thanks to you.
I quit being a cop.
You even went on the air
to give a special broadcast,
and I got absolutely roasted.
So I thought I'd bring you a gift.
Here.
Go on, open it.
I went to all this trouble.
[clicks tongue]
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
It's custom-made.
[chuckling]
Is this gold?
Yes.
One for you, one for Seongwon.
If you ever want to turn yourself in,
wear that to Gangha Police Station.
[sighs] Chairman Jin Myeongchul
was a good man,
but his son's a letdown.
You should worry about your own son.
How did you bring him up to be a murderer?
Nothing's holding me back now.
Being a detective
comes with a lot of restrictions.
I need to play by the rules
and keep the brass happy.
I don't have that anymore.
[scoffs]
Just watch and see how far I can go.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[door slams]
[scoffs softly]
[♪ music fades]
Are you busy, Mr. Chairman?
[exhales incredulously]
What brings you here?
You were eating.
[Mr. Choi sighs softly]
Are you here because of the broadcast?
I filed a correction
with the arbitration commission.
They won't listen.
What?
Chairwoman Jeong Taeseon
was just using me.
Why?
- Because her son is a killer...
- [gasps]
...and I'm going to catch him.
What are you talking about?
The artist Yu Seongwon is a killer?
Yes, a serial killer.
So I got fired today.
What?
I'm unemployed.
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
I did give in my resignation,
but I was basically fired.
Then what are you going to do?
[Isoo] Mmm...
Mr. Choi.
Don't we have some white hackers here?
We don't have any on staff,
but we have people under contract.
Set me up with them.
I'm going to arrest
Yu Seongwon and Jeong Taeseon both.
All right. I'll give them a call.
Ah.
Our subsidiaries advertise on UBS, right?
Cancel everything.
I'm going to sue for defamation.
[scoffs]
- Is that sushi?
- What? Oh.
[♪ music fades]
- [chuckles]
- [sighs contentedly]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
[engine purring smoothly]
Mmm!
Detective Jin Isoo!
- I'm a fan.
- Right.
[♪ music fades]
Really?
Yes.
Did you really kill Kim Younghwan?
No.
Oh, if you did, that'd be a killer story.
Can you stop talking about killing?
I heard you had a request for us.
Yes.
Find this person for me.
I think he's a close associate
of UBS's Jeong Taeseon.
He could be a former employee.
I can't find him in the company records.
Did this guy kill Kim Younghwan?
No.
[♪ jaunty, suspenseful music playing]
But he is a murderer.
He killed the guy
who killed Kim Younghwan.
- Oh!
- Oh! [chuckling]
[scoffs]
Can you find him without a name?
- Of course!
But before that, can I get your autograph?
Me too.
[♪ music fades]
[scoffs] Bring me a pen.
[♪ driving rock music playing]
JIN ISOO
DIRECTOR KIM IS HERE
[♪ music turns suspenseful]
[Taeseon's adviser]
Hansu pulled all their advertising.
I know. I heard.
They're even threatening a lawsuit.
We should issue a correction.
No, just leave it.
Pardon?
I said leave it. I'll handle it!
Yes, ma'am.
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
RETURN II
YU SEONGWON'S SOLO EXHIBITION
[director] Mr. Yu, welcome.
Yes, hello.
You're as handsome as always.
Have you been well?
Yes. I hope you've been well, too.
I've been so busy
getting the exhibition ready.
Come this way. We've set up the pieces.
What do you think?
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
For this exhibition,
that is the main piece.
It needs to be the first thing
people see when they walk in.
So vivid,
it almost seems alive.
FULL BLOOM, LIFE YET TO BLOOM
You get what I mean?
[chuckles softly] Yes.
[cell phone vibrating]
JEONG TAESEON
[sighs in exasperation]
- [Taeseon] Come to the office right now.
- [line disconnects]
[♪ music fades]
[door closes]
[inhales sharply]
We're meeting too often lately.
[muffled footsteps]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
I've got a plane ready,
so leave right now.
I can't cover for you any more than this.
If they look into Mr. Hwang,
everything will link back to you.
Then there's nothing I can do.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
Just stay out until I clean everything up.
I'm asking you.
Please!
If you really want it, then beg me.
[chuckling smugly]
Okay, fine.
It was a joke.
Fine.
I'll leave.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Okay, find out when and where
UBS' private jet is leaving today.
- Okay.
- [keyboard key clacks]
- [rapid digital beeping]
[digital beeps]
In two hours. Business aviation terminal.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
Yu Seongwon is flying out in two hours.
Where is he going?
[Isoo] I don't know,
but he's flying on a private jet.
Just go arrest him.
What will you do?
Dr. Seo said Yu Seongwon
would have kept all the evidence.
I'll go to his studio to find them.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Get ready to move out.
- Yes, ma'am.
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[engine purring smoothly]
[tires screech]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[distant jet engine roaring]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful, foreboding music playing]
[hammer clangs]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[creaking]
[♪ music turns ominous]
- [switch clicks]
- [light beeps]
[lights beep sequentially]
ECSTASY
A BREATHLESS FALL
JO NAYEONG
YU SEONGWON'S MODEL
CHOI YEONGMIN
CLIMAX
LIGHT SCATTERED ACROSS THE UNIVERSE
[Isoo] What's with the pebbles
and why stick the reed in?
DISSOLUTION
THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
KIM HEEJUN
YU SEONGWON'S JUNIOR
[♪ music swells]
FULL BLOOM, LIFE YET TO BLOOM
[♪ ominous chord swells, fades]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
JEONG MINJAE
FORMER DETECTIVE
[line connects, ringing]
- [siren blaring]
- [cell phone vibrating]
[Isoo] It's me.
I found Yu Seongwon's real studio.
All the evidence is here.
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
He found the evidence.
- [engine revving]
- [tires screeching]
[line connects, ringing]
Chief, I'm inside Yu Seongwon's studio.
There's a basement here.
I found the victims' belongings
and photographic evidence.
I'll send Forensics over, so wait there.
Yes, sir.
[music stops]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
- [engine roaring]
- [siren approaching]
[tires screech]
- [siren stops]
- [♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[scoffs]
Are you here to say goodbye?
Or have you grown attached to me?
[♪ gripping, ominous music playing]
- [Hyera] Yu Seongwon.
- [handcuffs clicking]
For the murders
of Jo Nayeong, Choi Yeongmin,
Kim Heejun, and Jeong Minjae...
[♪ melancholy piano music playing]
I am placing you under arrest.
[chuckles softly]
You sound confident.
Is it for certain this time?
Are you really sure
you can catch me?
[♪ ominous sting plays, fades]
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
[♪ melancholy piano music continues]
JIN ISOO
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
WHAT I HAD DRAWN WASN'T A HAT
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING TO GROWN-UPS
[cell phone vibrating]
We got him.
Okay.
I'll be there soon.
[Seongwon] After all,
you're my Little Prince.
[♪ music slows]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
[exhales softly]
Where is Isoo right now?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Did he go to my exhibition hall?
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
[♪ music swells]
[grunts, exclaims]
- [♪ music increases in tempo]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
- [clattering]
- [panting]
[exhales heavily]
[Isoo] Ah!
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Here you are, making a dramatic entrance.
[both grunting]
- [heavy thud]
- [glass shattering]
[♪ music swells]
[Isoo grunts]
[sighs in relief]
- [sharp whoosh]
- [Isoo exclaims]
[♪ gripping, dramatic music playing]
[both grunting]
[groaning]
- [clatters]
- [Isoo grunts]
[shattering]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
- [Isoo grunts]
- [heavy thud]
[groans]
- [blunt thud]
- [high-pitched ringing]
[thuds]
[distorted thud]
[♪ tense, ominous music playing]
- [hammer clangs]
- [exhales in relief]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[panting]
[Taeseon's assistant]
Jin Isoo is here inside the studio.
Burn him with it.
[liquid splashing]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[lighter clicks open]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music fades]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 13
WHAT FATE AWAITS ISOO?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
[Hyera] Chief.
What about Jin Isoo?
You'll wake up, right?
I know you won't let this break you.
Jin Isoo is still alive.
When it's done, leave the country.
[Taeseon's assistant] The basement
was destroyed. We won't find any evidence.
He's on the move with Yu Seongwon.
We're following them.
[Hyera] Detective Park! Detective Choi!
Yu Seongwon's gone. He ditched the car.
There's no choice. I'll finish this.
Do you get it now?
This is the death you love so much.
[laughing maniacally]
[Isoo] Yu Seongwon!
You crazy bastard.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ suspenseful, ominous music playing]
NUMBER 1 SAFETY!! NUMBER 1 PUBLIC ORDER!!
GANGHA POLICE STATION
[sighs softly]
[scoffs softly]
[♪ somber, ominous music playing]
[exhales softly]
Should I just disappear?
[scoffs softly]
Should I make one final piece?
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
Translated by Hyesoo Lee